Email: Ambliach@gmail.com

Summary

Human Resource Management and Philosophy double major adept and experienced in full life cycle recruiting, project management & talent development. Proven to be efficient, enthusiastic and versatile with strong professional communication, leadership, and administrative skills.

Education

Rutgers, The State University of New Jersey, New Brunswick, NJ B.A. in Human Resource Management and Philosophy (Double Major)

May, 2016

C: 609-865-8031

Work Experience

HR Manager

Always Best Care Princeton

04/2017-Present

- Created & implemented recruiting strategy for home health aids
- Decreased recruiting costs while increased eligible applicants
- Screen, interview and on-board all new employees
- Manage client and employee files to accreditation standards (responsible for raising agency to ACHC accreditation standards)
- Created work description for several different internal positions
- Trained and directed four interns\
- Assist with payroll (ADP) as well as employee troubleshooting with ADP workforce Now

Pharmacy Assistant

Marin Pharmacy

11/2014-04/2017

- Assisted and resolved various client issues leading to complete costumer satisfaction
- Inputted insurance reclaims
- Managed and ensured proper medication rotation

Recruiting Intern

Lorelei Staffing

5/2016-7/2016

- Screened and interviewed candidates for direct hire, contract, and contract-to hire opportunities
- Communicated with clients in a fast-paced, deadline driven environment
- Worked independently and as a team to foster professional growth for both candidates and clients

Maître d'hôtel/Waiter

11/2008-12/2014

Carlucci's Grill Italian Restaurant, West Windsor, NJ

- Trained six newly hired Maîtres d'hôtel
- Functioned as Assistant Manager on multiple occasions resulting in smooth operation of restaurant
- Facilitated restaurant organization, efficiency, and quality by leading and assisting wait staff
- Ensured restaurant profitability by improving customer relations and satisfaction

Intern

Summer 2013

Wilentz, Goldman and Spitzer PA

- Responsible for filing and organizing various case files
- Directed clients via telephone
- · Compiled and ordered large discovery documents

Trip to China (Independent)

Shenyang, Qingdao, Beijing

6/2/2012-7/18/2012

- Took Chinese classes in an independent academy in Shenyang, China
- Traveled alone to learn and experience the different cultures in the cities of Shenyang, Qingdao and Beijing, China

Activities and Skills

-HTML (beginner)

-Microsoft Office Suite

-ADP WFN (experienced)

-Spanish (conversational)

-CSS(beginner)

-Javascript (beginner)

-Rutgers Acappella/Choir President

-Chinese (some written, some spoken)